<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<compiereTrl baseLanguage="en_US" language="es_ES" table="OBUISEL_SELECTOR_FIELD" version="">
  <row id="E395C18AAFEF4FA7BD169D8D3B0F32E1" trl="N">
    <value column="Name" isTrl="Y" original="id">Work Requirement</value>
    <value column="Description" isTrl="N" original=""/>
    <value column="Help" isTrl="N" original=""/>
  </row>
  <row id="F7AD95B30BBD40FAAA08B82561695156" trl="Y">
    <value column="Name" isTrl="Y" original="Document No.">Nº documento</value>
    <value column="Description" isTrl="Y" original="An often automatically generated identifier for all documents.">Identificador de documentos que puede generarse automáticamente.</value>
    <value column="Help" isTrl="Y" original="The document number is usually automatically generated by the system and determined by the document type of the document. If the document is not saved, the preliminary number is displayed in &quot;&lt;&gt;&quot;. If the document type of your document has no automatic document sequence defined, the field will be empty when creating a new document. This is for documents which usually have an external number (like vendor invoice).  If you leave the field empty, the system will generate a document number for you. The document sequence used for this fallback number is defined in the &quot;Document Sequence&quot; window with the name &quot;DocumentNo_&lt;TableName&gt;&quot;, where TableName is the actual name of the table inside the database (e.g. C_Order).">El número del documento suele ser generado automáticamente por el sistema y está determinado por el tipo de documento del propio documento. Si no se guarda el documento, el número preliminar se muestra con "&lt;&gt;". Si el tipo de documento no tiene definido la generación automática del número éste quedará vacío al crear el nuevo documento. Puede ocurrir para aquellos documentos que tienen números externos(factura de venta). Si se deja vacío el sistema le generará un número. La secuencia de números utilizada en los documentos está definida en la ventana "Mantenimiento de la secuencia" con el nombre "Númerodocumento_NombreTabla", donde el nombre de la tabla es en nombre actual de la misma (p.ej C_Orde).</value>
  </row>
</compiereTrl>
